http://www.microcenter.com/site/customer-support/privacy_policy.aspx

Skip to Main Content Area
Breadcrumbs
Your privacy is important
June 30, 2020 – The California Privacy Rights section below was updated in compliance with the California Consumer Privacy Act.
This page discloses the privacy policy of Micro Electronics, Inc., Micro Center® and Micro Center Online®. We are concerned about your privacy and the security of your important personal information. We want you to be aware of what kind of information we obtain from you, how we use this information, and how you can control its use.
Micro Electronics, Inc. operates retail stores and web sites under the names of Micro Center and Micro Center Online. Micro Electronics, Inc. is the parent company of these companies, and as such, when you provide information to any of these entities, this information may be combined or shared between current or future Micro Electronics, Inc. entities and subsidiaries.
This site is restricted to users from the United States and those not governed by privacy policies of the European Union. Users from the European Union are advised not to disclose personal information on this site.
By using this site or making purchases at our stores, you consent to this Privacy Policy. You should also review our Safe Shopping Promise for online purchases.
How is personally identifiable information collected?
We collect and store information you provide in our stores and through our digital properties, primarily through the sales transaction and customer registration processes, but may also include other processes such as sweepstakes sign up, survey responses and email registration. We may also obtain personal and non-personal information from third-party providers.
To opt-out of any communications from Micro Center or Other Partner Companies, refer to the subscribe/unsubscribe sections below.
What personally identifiable information is collected?
In order to provide you superior service, communicate marketing promotions which we believe will be of interest to you, and to administer our business, Micro Center retail stores and Micro Center Online may gather the following personal information (except where prohibited by law): salutation, name (first/middle/last), billing and shipping addresses, company name (if applicable), email address, phone/fax number (if applicable), transactional information, payment type (VISA, Check, Cash, etc.), and other information you have provided or may provide in the future, or that we have received from 3rd parties.
To enhance your Micro Center Online experience, we also collect information as to which pages you visit, search terms used, etc. - in order to measure the effectiveness of our website and identify areas for improvement (product selection, site performance and/or to streamline the purchasing processes). We also collect this information to create a more personalized online shopping experience and personalized marketing campaigns based on your preferences.
How is the collected information used?
Micro Center retail stores and Micro Center Online use your personally identifiable information to provide superior service in the following areas: to process, fulfill and track online orders and in-store pickup reservations; bill your credit card for purchases; respond to your customer service inquiries or requests; provide requested services such as rebate redemption and warranty coverage; offer information regarding products and services based on your interests or past purchases; hold contests, giveaways, drawings and promotions; administer shopping or reward club accounts; conduct and administer surveys; communicate targeted marketing/sales material via print and digital means; set up commercial accounts; sign up for new credit card promotions; or use it for other general business purposes to further enhance our business relationship with you.
How do we use cookies and technology in our website?
Micro Center Online sets cookies on your computer to record certain information during your online visit (session). The benefit to you is the ability to save items added to your Shopping Cart and store them on our server for future reference (up to 30 days). These cookies do not gather sensitive information like your name, address, etc., if you do not specifically give that information to us voluntarily. If you have given us that information, cookies enable us to recall it (and save you the trouble of entering it all over again) each time you visit our site. Our web server collects the addresses of the web sites visitors came from before visiting our site, which browser was used to view our site, and search terms entered on our site. We track the pages visited to help us understand how customers use our site. This helps us make decisions on how to create a better experience for you in the future. At your option, if you delete our cookies, you will limit our ability to personalize the site for your next visit. However, deleting a cookie will not prevent you from visiting our site and making purchases.
Google Analytics
Our Site uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). This analytical tool uses cookies and similar technologies to help analyze how users use the Site. The information generated about Site usage, including visitor IP address, is transmitted to Google. This information is then used to evaluate visitors’ use of the Site, compile statistical reports on website activity, and provide other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also collect information about Site visitors’ use of other websites. Google offers the ability to opt out from tracking through Google Analytics cookies; for more information, visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Advertisers
We use outside advertising companies ("Advertisers") to serve advertisements on the Site. Please be advised that such Advertisers may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser (including through use of pixel tags). If you would like more information about this practice and to learn about your choices in connection with these practices, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp and http://www.aboutads.info.
You can visit the Network Advertising Initiative website to opt out of third-party cookies.
Who are the third party entities with whom we may share your personally identifiable information?
Third party service providers:
Micro Center retail stores and Micro Center Online may provide your name, address and email address to reputable organizations that help us to fulfill services to you on our behalf. For example, we may use such third party service providers to authorize credit card transactions, ship packages, activate gift cards and warranties, schedule and perform product installations, administer service programs, help us maintain records and analyze sales data, augment and improve the accuracy of our customer records, and distribute print and digital communications to you with our offers or important information on our behalf. None of these third party service providers are authorized to use your information for any purpose other than to provide the above stated services for which they contract with us to perform.
Links to Third Party Sites:
Micro Center Online contains certain links and ads to third party websites, such as our vendors’ websites and links to other websites intended to facilitate our customers’ shopping experience. We are not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content found on these websites. We recommend that you check the privacy notice of each website you visit. Links to third party websites are provided solely for your convenience and any submission of data to such websites shall be at your sole risk.
Other Partner Companies
We may occasionally share your name, mailing address and purchase information on a limited basis with select companies that offer products and services that may be of interest to you. We never share email addresses or telephone numbers with any of these third-party companies. If you prefer that we do not share your information with outside partner companies, you may so indicate as noted in the unsubscribe section below.
How do I unsubscribe from Micro Center sharing my information with other companies?
Unsubscribe Online
It's easy. Just access our Postal Preference Center to express your preferences.
Unsubscribe by Letter
Write to us and let us know what you would like to receive or not receive. You can send your letter to:
Communications Department, 4119 Leap Road, Hilliard, Ohio 43026
Note: Please be sure to include your full name, address and
phone number and tell us you want us to no longer provide your name and address
information to other companies. This will allow us to correctly identify you in
our systems and process your request.
Unsubscribe by Email
Email us at csrs@microcenterorder.com
Note: Please be sure to include your full name, address and phone number and tell us you want us to no longer provide your name and address information to other companies. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request.
How do I subscribe to / unsubscribe from Micro Center and Micro Center Online emails or postal mailings?
There are various methods for letting us know if you would or would not like to receive Micro Center and Micro Center Online postal or email promotions. (Please note that if you opt out of our email marketing communications, you may still receive business-related communications such as order and shipping confirmations, product recall information or other administrative communications.)
Subscribe / Unsubscribe Online
For email, visit our Email Preference Center where you can sign up to receive our various marketing promotions or request to no longer receive specified marketing promotions. All promotional emails we send you also contain a link allowing you to opt out of these specific emails in the future. Click on the relevant link and follow the simple instructions.
For postal, just access our Postal Preference Center to express your preferences.
Subscribe / Unsubscribe by Letter
Communications Department, 4119 Leap Road, Hilliard, Ohio 43026
Note:
Please be sure to include your full name, address and phone number and tell us you want us to no longer provide your name and address information to other companies. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request.
Subscribe / Unsubscribe by Email
Email us at csrs@microcenterorder.com
Note: Please be sure to include your full name, address and phone number and tell us you want us to no longer provide your name and address information to other companies. This will allow us to correctly identify you in our systems and process your request.
Subscribe / Unsubscribe In-Store
While visiting our retail stores, you may request to subscribe to or unsubscribe from our postal mailing lists. Please note; in order to adhere to legal guidelines involving unsubscribing from email, we cannot record your email preferences in store; this can only be accomplished through one of the other methods described above. If you opted out of receiving our postal or email marketing communications, please allow us a reasonable period of time to honor your request, as some promotions may already be in process. For email subscriptions, please allow up to a maximum of 10 business days for us to make the requested changes. Removal from our print advertising list may take up to 4 - 5 weeks, depending on the mailing cycle updating process. Of course, you always have the option to re-subscribe to our mailing lists By following the instructions listed above.
How do I make changes in the information I previously provided?
For registered
users, sign in using online account name and make changes to the information
you previously provided.
How do we protect the security of your Micro Center Online order information?
Micro Electronics, Inc. and Micro Center
Online are concerned about your privacy and the security of your important
personal information. We always use industry standard encryption technologies
when transferring and receiving any data that you exchange with our site. We
employ the same industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology that is
used by major banks and stock brokerage firms to conduct business via the
Internet. This encryption procedure "scrambles" the information you
send us and makes online transactions extremely safe.
Sensitive information, such as financial information, will
only be collected through secure web pages. Most browsers will display a green
"padlock" icon indicating you are browsing on a secure page.
We
have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to
protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have
collected from you via this site.
For complete details, please see our Safe Shopping Promise.
How do we handle information related to children?
This site is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly or intentionally obtain any personally identifiable information from any person we know to be under the age of 13.
California Privacy Rights
California residents may have certain privacy rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act ("CCPA") which apply in addition to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy.  California residents may learn more about their rights under the CCPA by clicking here.
How can you contact us with questions regarding this Privacy Policy?
If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by writing to: Micro Center Online at 4119 Leap Road, Hilliard, Ohio 43026 or calling Customer Support. Please remember to include your postal address, email address and phone number with your correspondence.
How am I notified of Privacy Policy changes?
As we continue to grow our businesses and improve our services, we reserve the right to change or modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If there are changes or additions, we will post them. If you disagree with any of those changes or additions, you may exercise the opportunity to opt out of receiving postal and/or digital promotion from us by using the procedures described below. If you are concerned about how your information is used, please check back at this site periodically.
This Privacy Policy is Currently in Effect.
Disclosure exceptions:
Notwithstanding the above policies, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information to appropriate third parties if we are required to do so by law or we believe that such action is necessary: to comply with legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order; to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our website and/or Micro Center Online; to protect Micro Electronics, Inc.'s rights and property; or during emergencies, such as when we believe someone's physical safety is at risk.
In addition, as we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer information, email addresses, and visitor information are generally among the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution, including, but not limited to, a bankruptcy proceeding. The effective date of this Privacy Policy is November 10, 2017.
DigiCert Authentic Site
Authentic Sites like microcenter.com use a DigiCert Secure Server Digital ID to offer proof of identity, to enable secure communications and to encrypt translations with site visitors through their web browser connections. The only way to be sure of a web site's authenticity is to view the site's Digital ID. Viewing a site's ID assures that you are not being "spoofed" (i.e. the site is real and not an impostor) since it contains:
The name of the company which owns the web site (e.g. Micro Electronics, Inc.)
The site's registered Internet address (e.g. www.microcenter.com)
The name of the Secure Server Certification Authority under which DigiCert issued the Digital ID (RSA Data Security or DigiCert)
We are using cookies to give you the best experience on our website. You can view our Privacy Policy and information reqarding our use of cookies here.
X Accept Privacy Policy and Terms
X Temporarily Hide Alert
